# **Shahanaj Parvin**

Dhaka, Bangladesh

shahanaj-parvin-931343137

+ (880) 1715852424

putulcse9@gmail.com

Experienced mobile app developer with 7 plus years of Android and iOS development expertise, along with 5 years of Flutter experience. Principles As a developer, take great pride in making sure all of the projects are to the client's satisfaction, all deadlines are met, and quality assurance is carefully considered. Placing customer satisfaction above all and promising to always deliver honest and speedy services.

#### SKILLS

## Programming Languages

Dart, JAVA, OBJECTIVE-C, Kotlin, C++, C

#### Flutter

Dart, RXDart, BLoc, Flutter Bloc, Rest API, Push Notification, State Management, Notification, Networking (HTTP, REST, DIO) Social Share, Video Player, Socket, Authentication, Testing

#### Database

SQLite, Moor, Realm

#### Others

Android, iOS, Material Design, Google Map, Push Notification Unit test, UI test and Integrationtest and CI/CD pipeline

MVVM, MVC, Clean architecture,

Clean Code, Refactoring, SOLID principle, TDD

Agile, Scrum, Sprint, BackLog

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science, Computer Science and Engineering** 2011-2015

Jatiya Kabi Kazi Nazrul Islam University Mymensingh, Bangladesh

#### **WORK HISTORY**

## **Senior Flutter Developer,** Bangladesh— Binate Solutions Nov 2019 – Present

- Currently working a social media mobile application by Flutter using Bloc architecture, Get it and auto routes.
- Managed end-to-end process including requirements, design, development, and testing.
- Integrated Push notifications (Android and iOS) as well as Local notifications for Android.
- Integrated REST APIs in the app.
- Worked with Socket connection for real time message communication.
- Independently worked on projects and maintained the code.

# **Mobile App Developer,** Bangladesh— Divine It Limited Feb 2016 - Oct 2019

- Worked on World class ERP system.
- Designed and developed applications following to roles of solid principle.
- Translate and build designs into responsive UI code.
- Used the MVVM architecture to meet product requirements.
- Managed the code and project on Git in order to keep in sync with otherteam members and managers.

### Author of CodeCanyon Platform, FlutterLover

Oct 2019 - PRESENT

- Develop high-quality mobile apps for iOS and Android by Flutter.
- Provide regular updates and bug fixes.
- Collaborate with clients for customized solutions.